wizst.com 2013-06-05

# wizst

Webika Ltd. ("wizst") owns and operates a number of different sites on the Web (each, an "wizst Site"). wizst is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information wizst may gather about individuals who visit the wizst Sites, how that information is used, and wizst's disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to the wizst Sites, and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links or to any software that may be downloaded from the wizst Sites.

## Anonymous User Information

wizst collects some anonymous information each time you visit an wizst Site so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience. We do not collect your IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type. You do not have to register with wizst before we can collect this anonymous information.

The wizst Sites do not require you to share information that identifies you personally, such as your name or e-mail address, in order for you to use the wizst Sites. The wizst Sites assign an anonymous ID number to your requests and links the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited the wizst Site, your search terms, and the links upon which you choose to click. Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information. wizst analyzes the information to examine trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

## Individual User Information

From time-to-time the wizst Sites request information from you that may identify you personally in addition to the anonymous information described above. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name, e-mail address, shipping address, and zip code), and demographic information (such as age, gender, occupation, and household income). wizst will not use or disclose your individual user information except as described in this privacy policy. wizst collects individual user information in the following ways from different wizst Sites:

## Surveys or Contests

From time to time, wizst may conduct surveys or contests on an wizst Site. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose individual user information to the wizst Site. Contest information will be shared with the contest or survey sponsors to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the wizst Site. We may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests. These companies may use your personal information to help the wizst Site communicate with you about offers from the wizst Site and our marketing partners. Such third parties do not have wizst's permission to use your personally identifiable information for any secondary purpose.

## Directory Services

wizst offers certain personalization services within its directory services (i.e., White Pages and Yellow Pages) that enable you to give us your geographic location so we can remember it for you when you return to use our service. For example, if we know that you are searching from Bellevue, Washington for a particular company, we will pre-populate the city and state fields with Bellevue and Washington. While you are not required to use this feature of the directory services, the information enables us to provide you with a more efficient experience on the wizst Sites. In addition, wizst allows you to update, correct any errors in the listings, or include yourself in the directory services. In order to make these modifications, you may provide wizst with certain individual user information that wizst will use, along with its affiliates and third party service providers, to modify and update your information in the directory services database.

Yellow Pages listings are supplied by Verizon SuperPages. To add or update your existing free basic Yellow Pages listing, please go to the following web site: https://snap.superpages.com/NASApp/Listing/control/ViewListing. To delete your listing, please call the customer service department at 1-800-428-8722, stay on the line without pushing any prompts, and a representative will assist you.

You may update or delete your White Pages listing by searching the White Pages to find your listing. Once you have located it, simply click the update or remove link. To verify your request, wizst will send an e-mail message to the address that you provide. Once you confirm the request, your listing will be updated or deleted. Please allow approximately 24 hours for the update to become active after we receive your confirmation.

## Tell-A-Friend

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about any of our sites, we ask you for your friend's name and e-mail address. wizst will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the wizst Site. wizst does not store the information related to your friends and the one-time e-mail sent pursuant to your input will be our only contact with that person for such input.

## Correspondence

If you contact wizst, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your e-mail address.

## Third Party Information Gathering

The wizst Sites include content and ads from third parties that may perform user activity tracking other than that described herein. For more information about each third party content provider, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please refer to such third party advertiser's privacy policy.

The wizst Sites contain links to other sites on the Web. Please be aware that wizst is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Cookies

wizst may set and access wizst or partner cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small data file that a Web site may send to your browser and which may then be stored on your system. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once you close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

We use cookie and web beacon technology to track which pages on the wizst Sites our visitors view and which Web browsers our visitors use. We may also use cookies to help us provide personalized features and preferences to you within various wizst Sites in a way that may be linked to individual user information that you elect to share with us. We also use "action tags" to assist in delivering the cookie. These action tags allow us to compile statistics and other data about our customers on an aggregate basis, by embedding a random identifying number on each user's browser. Then we track where that number shows up on our site.

## Sharing

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of wizst's or such wizst Site's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

wizst Sites may use third party service providers to serve ads and e-mails on our behalf. These companies may use technologies to measure the effectiveness of ads and e-mails and use information about your visits to the wizst Site so that we can provide a better search experience to you. For this purpose, we may also provide these third party service
